mnml.la 2019-12-18

# Terms — mnml

#### SHIPPING & DELIVERY

We ship domestically and internationally. All orders are shipped via USPS, FedEx or DHL. Standard shipping within the U.S. for orders over $19.99 is free. International shipping, for orders $99.99 USD and below, will be $20.00 USD. For orders $100.00 USD and above, DHL express shipping will be free.

Please allow up to 3 business days for us to verify and process an order. Please allow an additional 7-10 business days for delivery. For international shipments, please allow 7-10 days for delivery depending on destination and selected delivery service.

We reserve the right to cancel an order at anytime. Similarly, we reserve the right to request additional information from our customers for verification purposes.

We are not responsible for any lost, stolen, damaged merchandise or delayed delivery once we have shipped your order.  Once you have received a delivery confirmation number, any claims should be made with USPS, FedEx or DHL. We are not responsible for customs, duties, taxes or miscellaneous fees incurred from importing our products.

A tracking number is provided once an order is verified, processed and submitted to USPS, FedEx or DHL.

We reserve the right to change or update our shipping policies and procedures at any time without notification.

**Buyer is Importer of Record**

The goods will be imported on behalf of the consignee/buyer. The consignee authorizes mnml to import the goods on his behalf. Further, the consignee/buyer agrees mnml may delegate the obligation to import the goods on his behalf to a subcontractor (e.g. customs broker). The consignee will pay the taxes & duties in addition with the purchase price of the goods.

#### RETURNS // REFUNDS // EXCHANGES

We want you to be 100% satisfied with your purchase from mnml.  If for any reason you are not satisfied, we would be happy to issue a store credit for any returned merchandise. Returns/Exchanges are NOT accepted for sales items.

Returns must be postmarked and mailed within 30 days from receipt of merchandise. Merchandise must be unworn with the original tags attached and in original packaging (where applicable). 

International returns initiated due to refusal to pay duties and taxes will be subject to a $25 restocking fee which will be deducted from the refund amount.

Please include the original packing list with your return to avoid any delays in processing. Once the package is received, our warehouse will process the return, and you will be notified via email.

We reserve the right to correct, update or change our returns/refund/exchange policy at any time without notification.

Please visit [mnml.loopreturns.com](http://mnml.loopreturns.com/) to process a return. All returns and exchanges should be shipped via insured traceable mail in a secure package to the following address:

**mnml returns /  Quiet Logistics**

422 Hazelwood Logistics Center D

#### SALES TAX

All orders shipping to a California address are subject to a 9.25% sales tax fee. All orders shipping to an address outside California, are not subject to sales tax. All in-store purchases are subject to a 9.25% sales tax fee.

#### USER INFORMATION

You acknowledge and agree that you are solely responsible for the accuracy and content of information, including but not limited to name, email, shipping address and billing address provided to us via our website or at our retail locations.

#### TERMS OF USE

By using mnml.la, you are accepting all terms and agreements set forth on this website. We may, at any time without prior notification, change or update our terms of use. We do not guarantee that all information on our website is current, accurate, or complete; this includes but is not limited to pricing or availability of product. We reserve the right to correct, update or change information at any time without notification. We are not obligated to honor any misinformation regarding pricing or availability of product.

#### LIMITS ON PURCHASING

We do not authorize the purchase of our merchandise for resale purposes. We may, at our sole discretion, limit or cancel quantities purchased per person, per household or per order. We also reserve the right to limit or cancel orders which we deem, at our sole discretion, to be placed by dealers, resellers or distributors. These restrictions may include orders placed by or under the same customer account, the same credit card, and/or orders that use the same billing and/or shipping address. We also reserve the right to cease doing business with those customers violating this policy. We may modify this policy at any time without prior notice. This policy applies to all purchases made at our retail stores and on our online store. We reserve the right to correct, update or change information regarding this policy at any time without notification.

#### COPYRIGHT & TRADEMARK

All content contained on this website, including but not limited to logos, images, graphics, and text is the sole property of mnml and is protected by U.S. and international copyright law. Copy and print of pages of this website may be for personal, non-commercial use only. Use of our website, including reproduction and direct links, is strictly prohibited without prior written consent by owner.

This Privacy Policy is provided to explain how information is collected on our website and how that information is handled once it has been collected. This Privacy Policy may change at any time. By using mnml.la, you accept the terms and conditions outlined in this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use.

#### THE TYPE OF INFORMATION COLLECTED

There are cases where mnml may ask you for personal information, such as your name, address, telephone number, date of birth, email address, payment information, etc. We may do this for instance when you make a purchase through the Online Shop, respond to communications such as email, or for services that require registration such as to be included on our mailing list. We might also collect personal information from you about a third party, for instance if you ask us to ship product to a third party we may ask for the name, e-mail address, address, phone number, etc. of the recipient. That information will only be used for the specific purpose for which the information was provided and mnml will not further contact the third party unless the third party contacts us.

We may use “cookies” to gather information about your visits to our website and to enhance your experience. Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive and used by mnml.la to enhance your shopping experience by speeding up the browsing experience and website performance. Cookies also are used to personalize your experience while using mnml.la and remembering your information when you return to mnml.la. You can turn off all cookies, in case you prefer not to receive them. You also can have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you have to adjust your browser settings. Please note that when you have set your computer to reject cookies, it can limit the functionality of the website you visit and it’s possible that you do not have access to some of the features on the website.

We may collect “click stream” data (e.g. server address, domain name, etc.) and demographic or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender and interests) with Google Analytics to better understand our audience. This information may be combined with information you have provided to us thereby enabling us to enhance your experience.

#### USE OF INFORMATION

All personal information that we obtain about you will be recorded, used, and protected by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this Privacy Policy. We primarily will use your personal information to provide products and services to you (e.g. to process and ship your online order). mnml.la periodically will update customers via email about new product updates and promotions. If you wish to be removed from this email list, then please visit mnml.la and remove your email address by updating your personal information, or click the “unsibscribe” link at the bottom of an email you have received from us. (To update your personal information via the website, log onto mnml.la and click “My Account.” )

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer your personal information to third parties without informing you in advance and in accordance with applicable data protection law. Your data may be transferred to web site hosting partners and other parties who assist us in designing and operating the website, executing services, or analyzing collected data. These parties only will use your data for the purpose of carrying out the word as indicated and will be required to keep the information confidential. We also will release personal data without consent if such is required by law or for security purposes.

#### BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:  
FACEBOOK - https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads  
GOOGLE - https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous  
BING - https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/.

#### DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

#### SECURITY OF INFORMATION

The security of the information you provide to us is protected by various security measures we have implemented. Your personal information is maintained through secure networks and is only accessible by a limited number of people who have special access rights and are required to keep the information confidential. Notwithstanding mnml.la's efforts, no transmission of data over the Internet is guaranteed to be completely secure and such transmission is at your own risk.

#### LINKS TO THIRD PARTIES

For your convenience and to improve the usage of the website, we insert links to third parties, for which this Privacy Policy does not apply. These links take you outside our services and off the mnml.la website and are beyond our control. This includes links from parties that may use mnml logos as part of a co-branding agreement or sell mnml’s products. The sites you can link to have their own separate Privacy Policy and although we seek to protect the integrity of our site, mnml is not responsible and cannot be held liable for the content and activities of these sites. Your visit/access to these sites therefore is entirely at your own risk. Please note that these other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data or solicit personal information.

By using our website, you (the visitor) agree to allow third parties to process your IP address, in order to determine your location for the purpose of currency conversion. You also agree to have that currency stored in a session cookie in your browser (a temporary cookie which gets automatically removed when you close your browser). We do this in order for the selected currency to remain selected and consistent when browsing our website so that the prices can convert to your (the visitor) local currency.

#### CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 et. seq. permits customers of mnml who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following address: mnml 3325 Manitou Court Mira Loma, CA 91752 USA. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow up to 30 days for a response.

#### EUROPEAN PRIVACY RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

#### DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

#### LIMITATION OF LIABILITY

IN NO EVENT SHALL MNML, ANY OF ITS AFFILLIATES, OR ANY OF THEIR OWNERS, OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS BE LIABLE FOR ANY INDIRECT, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION UNDER CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE OR ANY OTHER THEORY, ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS WEBSITE. 

The laws of the State of California shall govern all matters relating to this website Privacy Policy, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of law.

#### SECURITY

Our site is completely secure and you should have no concerns with safety. All credit card information is transmitted over a secure connection.
